（忆往昔）
他们转化了我
They turned me.
恨死那些尖牙了
Hate those fangs.
她 她咬了我的脖子
She … she bit me in the neck.
咬一下倒没关系
The bite doesn't matter.
只有喝下血液 才会变成吸血鬼
You have to actually ingest the blood to be infected.
- 他给你喝的是吸血鬼的血 - 什么
- That was vampire blood he dosed you with. - What?
会怕光 阳光会灼伤皮肤
Lights are too bright? Sunshine hurt your skin?
我觉得好饿
I get so hungry.
- 你都在干些什么 - 猎魔 跟别人一起
- What have you been doing? - Hunting … with some other people.
你 竟然跟陌生人共事
You? Working with strangers?
他们更像是家人
More like family.
我是你的外公
I'm your grandfather.
有空我教你 这可是你老爸梦寐以求的本事
Stick around, I'll show you tricks your daddy never even dreamed of.
我 只是无法抛下你和本
I-I can't just lose you and Ben.
我和本会呆在这儿 只要可以你随时都能来
Me and ben will be here, and…You come when you can.
答应我完好无损地回来
Just come in one piece.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
当然 我很好
Yeah, I'm great.
因为有好几次 你让我觉得很纳闷
'cause there's been a few times that you've got me wondering.
是萨姆 鲍比 他有点儿不一样了
It's Sam, Bobby. He's just … he's different.
让我觉得有点儿不对劲
Something's not right to me.
（如今）
（1989年9月9日出生 艾米莉·方 林肯大街315号 灰岩镇 伊利诺州）
你来了
You came.
我答应过你的
I told you I would.
找个地方坐吧
Shall we sit?
我不能告诉你
I can't tell you that.
太尴尬了
Too embarrassing.
没关系
Come on.
无论你说什么都不会…
Nothing you could ever say would…
我是说 你发表的那些诗
I mean, those poems you posted?
正是你最真自我的体现
They revealed who you really are.
我了解你 克里斯滕
I know you, Kristen.
谢谢
Thanks.
我其实
I actually, um…
今天又写了一首 你想不想…
wrote one today. You want to…?
我十分乐意拜读
Of course I do.
嗷 该死的
Ow. Damn it.
被纸划伤了
Paper cut.
我真是个笨手笨脚的人
Hi, clumsiest person ever.
我必须得走了
I have to go.
等等
Wait!
- 嘿 - 你好
- Hi. - Hi.
我不该来的
I shouldn't be here.
那你怎么又来了
So why are you?
你在我脑海里挥之不去
I can't stop thinking about you.
那么
Then…
就一直想着我吧
Don't.
我们不能这样
We can't do this.
我们没法厮守的
We can't be together.
- 一定有其他办法的 - 没有
- There has to be a way. - No.
你觉得你了解我
You think you know me…
其实不然
but you don't.
我简直作恶多端
I've done bad things.
你该逃得远远地
You should run.
马上
Now.
我可以自己拿主意
I can make my own decisions.
我已经十七岁了
I'm 17.
我得让你看样东西
I have to show you something.
好的
Okay.
我就知道
I knew it.
- 你害怕吗 - 不怕
- Are you scared? - No.
你应该害怕的
You should be.
我只是害怕
I'm just scared…
我这是在做梦 等我醒来发现是在上数学课
I'm dreaming and I'll wake up in math class.
那很痛吗
Is it gonna hurt?
我绝对不会伤害你的
I could never hurt you.
跟我来
Come with me.
去哪儿
Where?
带你去看看我的世界
Let me show you my world.
埃基
Edgee.
你住的地方…
So, your place…
是不是有 丝绒呢
is there gonna be… velvet?
是的 当然有
Yeah, sure.
就是这儿吗
This is it?
但是 味道好难闻啊
But… It smells like pee.
干得漂亮 小罗
Nice work, Robbie.
罗伯特 怎么回事儿啊
Robert, what's happening?
这不正是你想要的吗
This is what you wanted, isn't it?
嗯 我就快到家了
So, uh, I'm actually not far.
大概再开一晚
I'm about a night's drive.
是吗 那么你是想
Yeah? So, you think…
是的 不过得先办妥这儿的事
Well, there's some stuff I got to do here first.
当然
Of course.
不过我在想 这边办妥之后
But I was thinking that, uh, I'll wrap up here.
你知道的 要确保没被跟踪
and, you know, make sure I'm not followed.
我得绕着僻路走
I'll have to take side streets,
而且只能深夜回去…
and I'd have to come at night …
你可不可以给我闭上嘴 乖乖滚回来就好
Will you just shut up and get your ass home?
我迫不及待想见你 只能通电话实在很烦人
I can't wait to see you. This phone thing's getting old.
好的
Yeah.
快到时就打给我们
Well, call us when you're close.
还有小心点儿
And be careful.
好的
Of course.
什么事让你这么荡漾
What are you so stoked about?
啥 没什么 有什么发现
What? Nothing. What do you got?
七天里有六个姑娘失踪
Six girls in seven days,
超过了这个镇一年的失踪人口数了
which is more disappearances than this city has seen in over a year.
而且都是同龄人
All about the same age.
而且全都很可爱
And cute.
萨姆 这世界可是五光十色的啊
Hey, ice cream comes in lots of flavors, Sam.
懂了
Right, sure.
6个女孩
Yeah, well, half a dozen girls,
十七八岁 接近成年
late teens, a shower away from greatness.
听上去受害者都很相似
Sounds like a profile.
真好奇她们还有什么共同点
Wonder what else they got in common.
有6个切入点
Well, six directions to go, here.
选一个吧
Pick a number.
7 今天又增加了一个
Seven. Another call just came in today.
克里斯滕是个好孩子 的确有点幼稚
Kristen's a good kid … a little naive, sure.
我尽量做一个好爸爸
You try and be a good parent.
女孩子真让人头疼
Girls are hard.
额 我们只想找到你女儿
Right. Well, we'd just like to find your daughter.
左边最后一间
Last door on the left.
谢谢
Thanks.
你觉得他在说什么啊
What do you think he was talking about?
嗑药吗
Drugs?
比嗑药可严重多了
Oh, it is so much worse.
吸血鬼
Vampires?
这些不是吸血鬼
These aren't vampires, man. These …
这些是傻逼
these are douchebags.
没错
Yeah.
好吧
All right.
看看有什么线索
Let's see what we can see.
好的
All right.
这个 让人太不舒服了
That … that's just… uncomfortable.
他装什么忧郁王子啊
What is he so bummed out about?
看这个
Look at this.
偷看人家女孩睡觉 不是变态是什么
He's watching her sleep. How is that not rapey?
迪恩 我需要全神贯注
I got to concentrate here, Dean.
「他能听见鲜血在她体内流淌」
"He could hear the blood rushing inside her,
「舌头似乎尝到了那绝妙的味道」
"almost taste it.
「他拼命地想控制自己」
"He tried desperately to control himself.
「罗梅罗知道他们相爱无果」
Romero knew their love was impossible."
罗梅罗 不是吧
Romero? Really?
迪恩 闭嘴
Dean. Shut up.
这还是全国畅销书
This is a national bestseller.
怎么可能
How is that possible?
试试「洛特纳」（《暮光之城》中饰演狼人雅各布·布莱克）
Hey, try, um… "Lautner".
等等 他是狼人吧
Wait. He's a werewolf.
再说你怎么知道他的
How do you even know who that is?
搞笑呢啊 那娃无处不在
What, are you kidding me? That kid's everywhere.
简直就是噩梦
It's a freaking nightmare.
帕丁森（《暮光之城》男主角）的名字里有多少个「T」
Hey, how many t's are there in Pattin…
正解 密码破解了
That's it. We're in.
好了
All right.
有什么发现
Well?
她的收件箱全是一个
Well, her in-box is full.
自称是吸血鬼的家伙的来信
from some guy claiming to be a vampire.
- 真正的吸血鬼 - 这个…
- A real vampire? - Well, uh…
「我只能在晚上和你见面」
"I can only meet you at night.
「 我不太放心自己和你在一起 」
"I don't trust myself with you.
「我无法抵抗你鲜血的诱惑」
The call of your blood is too strong."
吸血鬼网钓猎物吗
Vampires phishing for victims?
也有可能是一个闲的蛋疼的人类
Probably just a human mouth-breather, right?
换句话说 这样捕猎多方便啊
On the other hand, talk about easy prey.
对于真正的吸血鬼来说
For actual vamps.
对 这些女孩
Yeah, I mean, these chicks.
自己投怀送抱
are just throwing themselves at you.
你只需要…
All you got to do is…
写点蹩脚的诗 她们就上钩了
I don't know. Write bad poetry.
这人想和她
Well, this guy wanted to meet her.
在一个叫「黑玫瑰」的地方见面
at a place called the Black Rose.
不嘞个是吧
Give me a break.
我只是照着读出来
I'm just reporting the news.
也可能就是个变态 对吧
It's probably just your standard-issue perv, right?
住手
Stop!
放开我
Let me go!
（献血光荣）
你肯定是吸血鬼干的
Ok, so you're sure it's vampire.
- 百分之百吗 - 当然
- 100%? - Definitely.
典型吸血鬼行为
We got a pattern now …
受害人失踪 捐血车被洗劫一空
kids go missing, blood-bank van gets jumped.
这是第四个镇子了
This is the fourth town.
确凿的证据就是最近那个案子
Clincher is, this last hit …
司机被发现时 喉咙被撕裂了
driver was found, throat ripped out.
他们抓孩子 来吸血 对吧
Okay, they grab kids … that's food, right?
但是 如果他们
But if they already got.
已经有了新鲜的血液
a bunch of walking, talking juice bars,
干嘛还要抢劫捐血车
why bother with the blood mobile?
这就怪了
It doesn't add up.
找到他们的老巢 去找答案
Find the nest. Figure it out.
想要摇滚妞儿的话 这儿一大片
Well, you wanted emo chicks. I think we hit ground zero.
谢谢
Thank you.
她在沙滩上也穿成那样吗
Think she wears all that rubber at the beach?
我们上次在一起喝酒是什么时候了
When's the last time we had a beer together, anyway?
看那边
There.
你怎么看
What do you think?
他很努力在泡那女孩
He's hitting on her hard enough.
会是吸血鬼吗
Real?
我不知道 很难说
I don't know, it's hard to tell.
又多一组嫌疑人
And we got multiple choice.
这下可好 他们三个人 我们两个人
Great. Three of them, two of us.
好了 三人组变两人组
Okay, make that two of them.
有一个已经动身了
One's on the move.
好吧 你跟那个80后 我跟那个90后
All right, you go with Efron. I got Bieber.
亲爱的 你确定吗
Are you sure, baby?
你准备好加入我的永恒国度了吗
Are you ready to join me in eternity?
求之不得
Oh, my god, totally.
走 离开这里
Go! Get out of here!
- 你干什么啊 - 张开嘴巴
- What the hell are you doing?! - Open your mouth!
把那东西拿出来
Take those out.
拿出来
Take 'em out!
真恶心 都多大了还玩这套
For the love of… What are you, 12?
你是还擦闪粉了是吗
Are you wearing glitter?
我不过是想把个妹玩玩
I only do it to get laid, man!
那玩意儿有用吗
Does it work?
我嘞个去
I'll be damned.
好啦 回去打你的炮吧
All right, "Mmmbop" your way out of here.
走啊 快点
Go! Go.
记得带套
And use a condom.
真是个尤物啊
You're pretty.
你刚说啥
I'm sorry?
我说你
I said…
真是个尤物
"You're pretty."
哦 真是抱歉
Yeah. Sorry again, pal.
哥是直男
I don't play for your team.
住手
No!
小萨姆
Sammy.
我的亲娘 什么鬼声音啊
Oh, my god, what is that sound?
哪有什么声音 迪恩
What sound, Dean?
怎么回事
What?
搞毛啊 小声点 擦的了
Hey, come on! Keep it down, damn it!
拜托把灯关掉
Please, please shut that off.
上帝啊
Oh, geez.
迪恩 你快坐下
Dean, you should sit down.
你管我
You sit down.
我设想过千万种死法
Out of all the ways to die,
唯独没料到会落入这般田地
I never thought I'd be going out like this.
迪恩 你会没事的
Dean, nobody is going out.
怎么了
What?
萨穆埃尔一来 我就必死无疑了
Samuel's gonna kill me when he gets here.
不 迪恩 他不会的
No, Dean, he's not.
他会的 因为我会要他杀了我
Yes, he is, 'cause I'm gonna ask him to.
我知道你下不了手
because you won't do it.
别这样 先等等
Okay, just hold on a second.
等什么 看我现在人模鬼样的
For what, huh?! Look at me!
- 我们会想出办法的 - 什么办法
- We can figure this out! - How?!
你怎么一点都不怕
Why aren't you freaked out?
- 我吓坏了 - 真的吗
- Of course I am! - Really?
你的心跳我可是听得一清二楚
'Cause I can hear your heartbeat,
稳得令人发指
and it's pretty damn steady.
那是因为我 我在努力使自己保持冷静
That's 'cause I'm … I'm trying to remain calm.
迪恩 听着 萨穆埃尔知道该怎么做
Dean, look, Samuel will know what to do.
别做梦了 我现在就是个怪物
Come on, man. I'm a monster, okay?
情况远没你想得那么轻巧
This is not a problem that you spitball.
我们得在我伤害别人之前做个了结
We got to deal with this before I hurt somebody.
你什么感觉
How's it feel?
现在吗
Now?
这个时候你跟我谈感觉
Now you want to talk about my feelings?
我是说生理上的
I-I mean physically.
能有什么感觉 糟透了
How do you think it feels? Not good!
你去哪儿
Where you going?
厕所 行不
Bathroom, okay?
简讯简讯 大法师 吸血鬼想嘘嘘了
News flash, Mr. Wizard … vampires pee.
迪恩
Dean?
Dean.
是我
Hey.
嗨
我以为你还得再等几天才回来呢
I wasn't expecting you for a couple of days.
是啊
Yeah, yeah.
我想见见你
I wanted to see you.
怎么了
What's up?
你还好吧
Are you okay?
- 听我说 - 究竟怎么了
- Listen. - What's going on?
那都无所谓
It doesn't matter.
我就是想告诉你
But I need you to know …
你和本
You and Ben.
那个
Just, uh…
感谢你们
Thanks. Okay?
所做的一切
For everything.
迪恩 你吓到我了
Dean, you're scaring me.
老天 我成了帕丁森（《暮光之城》男主角爱德华扮演者）了
Oh, god, I'm Pattinson.
什么
What?
没什么 我 我得走了
Nothing. I-I-I got to go.
不许走 你不能露个脸就…
No. No, you can't just show up here like this and then …
- 相信我 我也情非得已 - 住嘴
- Believe me, I wish it was different. - Just stop!
把话说清楚 到底怎么回事
And explain to me what's going on out there.
莉莎 这简直一团糟 我不能把你扯进来
Lis, I can't bring this crap home to you.
你是指你的工作
You're talking about your work.
我说的是我的生活
I'm talking about my life.
阴暗恐怖
It's ugly.
血风腥雨
And it's violent.
我就快死了
And I'm gonna die. Soon.
告诉我
Just tell me.
快告诉我你究竟怎么了
Just tell me what the hell is going on.
迪恩
Dean?
我得走了
I got to go.
迪恩
Dean?
本 别过来
Ben, just stay there.
我好想听到你说…
I thought I heard you …
我让你站住
I said stay back!
你连你哥都看不住么
You can't keep track of your brother now?
我觉得他不会…
Well…I mean, I didn't think he'd just …
他变了 萨姆
He's not himself, Sam!
他现在就是头饥饿难耐的怪兽
He's a monster, and he's hungry.
我得准备一下 把这事儿做个了断
I've got to prepare to do the right thing.
我就说他一来就会把我给灭了
I told you he'd kill me when he showed up.
你吸血了吗
Did you feed?
我去和莉莎道别来着
I went to say goodbye to Lisa.
事实证明 还真是个烂主意
Which, for the record, is a lousy idea.
迪恩 回答我
Dean, answer the question.
放心 我没喝任何人的血
You can relax. I didn't drink anyone.
谢天谢地
Thank god.
但我快忍不住了
But I came close.
好了
All right.
动手吧
Do it.
你执意要死也可以
Okay. If you insist.
或者让我把你变回来
Or I can just turn you back.
- 什么 - 你说什么
- What? - What?
我大老远开车过来不是要杀你的 迪恩
I didn't drive all this way to kill you, Dean.
我是来救你的
I'm here to save you.
这是我爷爷的手记
That's my grandfather's journal.
解药是坎贝尔家的秘方
Cure's an old Campbell recipe.
有点像汤剂
Kind of like the soup.
从来没人试过
No one's tried it since god knows.
就我所知 这玩意是段恶性迷幻旅程
From what I hear, the stuff is a bad trip.
真有他的
Awesome.
解药本身没问题 但关键在你
Hey, the cure is good. But a lot of this is on you.
你只要碰了人血就没救了 解药不会起作用的
You drink, you're done. It won't work.
哪怕只是一小滴人血都不行
I'm talking one drop of human blood.
- 明白了 - 真的吗
- I got it. - Do you?
你终究会嗜血的 只是时间早晚而已
Because you will feed. It's a matter of time.
还需要什么
What else do we need?
有的已经有了 有的还要准备
Some stuff we got, some we got to get.
最关键之处在于
Trickiest thing on the list …
把你变成吸血鬼的那家伙的血
blood of the Fang who turned you.
他可不好对付
That guy was huge.
这药方上没一样东西是容易应付的
There's nothing in the recipe about easy.
你打算直接闯进他们的老巢吗
You're gonna walk right into the nest?
现在我跟他们一样了 不是吗
Well, I'm one of them, aren't I?
我只要大步往里走
So all I got to do is get in there,
趁他孤立无援时
get the guy alone, and…
给他多来点死人血
shoot him with so much dead man's blood.
他就能体会什么叫兄弟之情了
he'll think he's rushing a fraternity.
我跟你一起去
I should come with you.
不行 兄弟你气味太明显了
No. Dude, you reek.
你就跟个人肉大汉堡似的
You're like a walking hamburger.
我必须一个人去
I got to do this solo.
可我们还不知道他老巢在哪里
Yeah, except we haven't been able to find him yet.
不是问题 我能闻到他们的味道
No problem. I can smell them.
就在镇上往东两英里
They're two miles east of town.
你们带上其他材料在那里跟我汇合
You guys get the other crap and meet me there.
迪恩
Dean!
这是死人血
It's dead man's blood.
足够你对付两三个小喽罗了
Now, there's enough there to drop a linebacker and then some.
好运 孩子
Good luck, son.
你咋回事 萨姆
What the hell's wrong with you, Sam?
啥意思
What do you mean?
- 你明明知道解药的事 - 什么
- You knew about the cure. - What?
我咋可能知道
No, I didn't.
我们几个月前谈论过
Thought we talked about it, months ago.
不是跟我吧 可能是克里斯蒂娜
Not me. It must have been Christian or something.
是吗
Huh.
怪事了 如果你事先就知道
That's strange, 'cause if you had known,
那就像是你故意让他变成吸血鬼的
it'd be almost like you let him get turned.
你想找人打入内部
Get a man on the inside,
好帮我们找到吸血鬼始祖
help us find that alpha vamp we've been looking for?
你真这么想
You serious?
你觉得我会让我亲哥哥这样冒险
You think I'd do something like that, risk my own brother?
你才咋回事呢
What's wrong with you?
听着 我只是很庆幸我们能治好他
Look, I'm just relieved we can fix him.
什么事
What's up?
那个 我
Hey. Uh, I'm …
伯里斯在酒吧外转变的那家伙是吧
The guy Boris turned outside the bar, right?
他交代要好好关照你
He said to look out for you.
就是我
Yeah.
很高兴你成功了 伙计
Well, glad you made it, man.
跟我来
Follow me.
你肯定饿坏了吧
So, you must be starving.
就这包了
Here you go.
现在不用
I'm okay.
我来的路上干掉了很多人
I killed so many people on the way over here, so…
说起杀人
Yeah, uh, about that.
组织上的规定 我们不能再无故杀人了
Company line is we don't just kill people anymore.
但你一定得告诉我那感觉如何
But you got to tell me what that's like.
一定
Yeah.
一有机会 我就表演给你看
Yeah, first chance I get, I'll … I'll show you myself.
一言为定
Sweet.
别怕他们
Don't worry about them.
他们只是在嫉妒
They're jealous.
招募者能和小妞们嘿咻
The recruiters get to bang all the chicks.
这次就是你了
That's you now, bro.
- 招募者 - 是啊
- Recruiters? - Yeah.
老大会跟你解释的
Big man will explain.
稍等一下
Be with you in a minute.
你的肌肤有如夜晚的天鹅绒
"Your skin is the black velvet of the night."
很好 那小妞肯定吃这套
Nice. That stupid bitch will eat that up.
巴不得赶紧跟我们见面了
She'll be dying to meet.
自己去喝点血 甜心
Go get yourself some blood, sweetheart.
然后带上你的小屁股回来 好吗
Then march that little ass right back here, okay?
感谢上帝
Thank goodness.
我还以为那猎人把你脑袋砍下来了
I thought the hunter chopped your pretty head.
没 我跑得快
No, I got away.
抱歉 什么猎人
Sorry, what's a hunter?
要是他找到我们 你就明白了
You'll see, if he finds us.
等着看他被剖膛开肚吧
You'll see him inside out.
你喝过血了吗
You eaten?
喝过了
Yeah.
很好
Good.
会派上用场的
You'll need your strength.
有啥用
For?
罗伯特没告诉你吗
Robert didn't tell you?
你觉得我多大了
How old do I look?
三十三
Uh, 33?
差太远了
You're off.
已经六百多岁了
By about…six centuries.
我做了六百年吸血鬼
And these are the best days in the last 600 years.
现在是最好的年代
to be a vampire.
什么德古拉 什么安妮·赖斯 都是浮云
Dracula, Anne Rice? Please.
这帮小屁孩饥渴得很
These stupid little brats are so horny,
在她们眼里 咱就是开着跑车的王子
they reinvented us as prince charming with a Volvo.
她们想要吸血尖牙作为定情信物
They want a promise ring with fangs.
我就满足了她们
So I give it to 'em.
你出去钓几个漂亮妞
You … you go out, you get them,
再给我带回来
and you bring 'em home to me.
为什么要关在笼子里
So what's with the cages?
只是在她们乖乖听话前的约束而已
Oh, that's just, you know, till they're compliant.
最终这些妞也要出去
Eventually, these girls will go out,
钓一些你这样的帅哥回来
and they'll fetch me boys like you.
就这样不断发展壮大
And around and around we go.
不得不说 相当完美
I got to say, I'm impressed.
这整个系统 都是你建立的吗
This whole system, that's … that's all you?
不不不 不是我
no, no, no, no, no.
我只是个执行者 明白不
No, I just implement, you know?
确保你们自觉行事的
Make sure that you all fall in line.
都是他
It's his.
我们父亲建立的
Our father's.
你们的父亲
Hmm. Your father's?
你好奇心还真重啊
Aren't you the curious one.
比你想象得还要好奇
Oh, you don't know the half of it.
等时机成熟
In due time.
美人
You, uh…
想不想和我共游一回
You want the private tour, don't you?
我情何以堪啊
Thought you'd never ask.
想耍我吗 小子
You playing games with me, boy?
父亲
Father!
抓住他
Go get him!
应该就是这里了
This must be the place.
这卧底动静也太大了
So much for undercover.
进去吧
Let's go.
你该知道 你阻止不了的
You've stopped nothing. You know that?
他可比你我强大得多
This is much bigger than you and me.
你哥果然还是坎贝尔家的人
Looks like your brother has some Campbell in him after all.
迪恩 你没事吧
Dean, you okay?
没事
Yeah, I'm good.
如果有效 过程可不会很轻松
If this works, it's not gonna be a kiddie ride. You know that.
正合我意 来吧
That's great. Light her up.
你在里面发现什么了
So what did you see in there?
- 什么 - 吸血鬼老巢有发现什么
- What? - In the nest. What did you see?
萨姆 我听不清你说话
Sam, I can't hear you.
你血流的声音太他妈震耳了
Your…your blood is so freaking loud, okay?
退后点
Just…just back off.
把解药给我
Give me the damn cure.
活着万岁
L'chaim.
我不觉得
I don't think it…
成功了吗
Is it working?
不成功就要成仁了
Either that or he's dying.
早啊 昨天发现什么没
Hey. So, what did you see?
什么
What?
在吸血鬼老巢 你发现什么没
In the nest. What did you see?
我还在努力回想
Um, well, I'm still trying to work through it,
但肯定的是
but, uh, I'm pretty sure.
他们不是独立组织
they're not figuring out anything on their own.
有接受上头的命令
They're getting their orders from the top.
该做什么怎么做之类的
Where to go next, everything.
你说的上头是指
The top as in…
他们的始祖
Their Alpha.
至少我是这么觉得
At least, that's what I think it is.
他们之间有心灵感应
They've got some sort of psychic thing happening.
传达着某种指示
And he sends them, uh … I don't know … messages.
什么指示
Saying what?
实话实说吗
Honestly?
招募新人变成吸血鬼
Recruitment drive.
他们的始祖在组建吸血鬼大军
Their Alpha's building an army.
太让人「振奋」了
Well, that's comforting.
这还不是最糟的
That's not the worst.
还有什么更糟的
Then what is?
他们不再畏惧我们了
We don't scare them anymore.
我是莉莎
You've reached Lisa.
请留言 谢谢
Leave me a message. Thanks.
莉莎
Hey, Lis.
继续留言 请按键1
To continue recording, press 1.
删除请按
To erase …
跟莉莎聊得怎么样
How did it go with Lisa?
没打通
It didn't.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
没事
Yeah.
至少
At least, uh…
我还有你
You got my back.
不管发生什么 我都可以指望你
No matter what happens, I can always count on you,
对吧 小萨姆
rght, sammy?
当然了 迪恩
Yeah. Of course, Dean.